It's cute.
かわいいね
Awesome.
すげえ
That's nice.
それ、いいね
That's good.
いいよね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Do you have any costumes for when you are currently active?
今、活動してる時の衣装とかある?
The costume is a uniform.
衣装は制服でやってます
It's a uniform.
制服なんだ
What kind of uniform?
どんな制服?
It's like a formal outfit.
制度派服みたいな
Well, it's close to this.
まあ、こういうのに近い
yes.
はい
Are you used to the camera?
カメラは、じゃあ、慣れてる?
Let's be nervous.
緊張しよう
Have you ever been photographed?
撮られたりとかがある?
there is.
あります
I'm not at all confident.
全然、思いっきりしてない
It's getting hard, a little.
固くなってるやん、ちょっと
Are you going to have a handshake event?
握手会とかするんでしょ?
I will.
します
So, you're definitely used to that sort of thing.
じゃあ、全然、そういうの慣れてるよね
A handshake, ah.
握手、あっ
My hands are so sweaty.
手汗すごいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm sweating a lot.
すごい汗かいてる
My hands are small, a little.
手がちっちゃいよ、ちょっと
Well then, it's like this, Usubun.
じゃあ、なんかさ、こういうさ、薄分
It's like cutting your hair.
髪をさ、する感じで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
There are commercials like this, right?
こういう、ほら、CMとかあるでしょ
Well then, just a little.
じゃあ、ちょっとね
Massage.
マッサージね
Shall I give you a massage?
マッサージしようか
I was touched like this
こういう触られたりした
of?
の?
Have you ever been touched like this?
こう いう 触 ら れた り した の?
Is this good?
これ、いいの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Have you ever caught a glimpse of something like this?
こういうのチラッと見ちゃったことあるんでしょ?
No.
ないです
On stage.
ステージで
There is, right?
あるでしょ?
do not have.
ない
What kind of government is the school?
学校はどんな政府なの?
Convenience store teacher.
コンビニの先生
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I don't hate it.
嫌がってないもんね
No.
ダメ
Have you ever touched it?
触ったことあるんでしょ?
amazing.
すごい
Don't say it anymore.
もう言わずに
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Will you touch me?
触ってくれるの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
copper?
どう?
voice.
声
It might be big.
大きいかも
Maybe it's big?
大きいかも?
I'm still not sure.
ちょっとまだわからないんですけど
That's amazing.
すごいね
Does your hair always look like this?
いつもこうした毛なの?
I made this underwear myself.
この下着は自分で
I don't know.
分かんない
Don't you want it for yourself?
自分で欲しくなんない?
買
Would you like to go to
い に行きたいかな
This is amazing.
すごいね、これ
Shikka
しっか
the law of nature.
り
Did someone like this do it?
こんな 人やったの?
You also take photos like this, right?
こういう撮影もするでしょ?
In a group.
グループで
I don't like it.
嫌わ
I'm talking a little.
ちょっと喋ってる
I haven't.
してない
Haven't you?
してない?
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
What is it with my boyfriend?
彼 氏とさ、 なんだっけ?
At home?
おうちで?
Is your house big?
お うち大したの?
kiss.
ちゅう
What did you do?
ちゅうした?
amazing.
すごい
Erotic.
エロい
You're such an adult.
めちゃくちゃ大人だね
Not an adult.
大人じゃない
He's an adult.
大人だよ
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
tickles.
くすぐったい
It seems ticklish.
くすぐったいらしい
I've taken my clothes off so far.
ここまで脱いでるんだから
Isn't it a nuisance?
邪魔でしょ?
Because it's a big deal.
せっかくだから
Because I smelled it.
匂い嗅いだから
It's just a lot of experience.
いろんなこと経験のみだからね
I'm not surprised.
びっくりしないよね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Do you want me to touch you?
触ってもらう?
Why don't you do it for me?
やってあげないの?
Yeah.
うん
No, I have to do it.
だめだ、やってあげないと
Because it makes me happy.
喜ぶから
Hey, it's true.
ちょ、本当だね
No.
ダメ
Such a cute eye candy.
こんな、かわいいまつまいで
hey
ね
picture.
え
That's erotic.
エ ロいね
Is there a way to dress like this?
こういう恰好し方ある?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Yes, you haven't heard.
はい、聞いてないよね
Well then, more.
じゃあ、もっと
No.
ダメだよ
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
That's no good.
ダ メだよ
Stop it properly.
ちゃんとやめて
No beat yet.
まだ、ビートないよ
In the end, one day I really came back.
結局、いつか本当に帰ってきちゃった
No, it almost stinks.
違う、臭いくらい
You're still back, aren't you?
まだ、帰ってきたよね
It's scary, a little.
怖いな、ちょっと
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Are you let in now?
今、入れられた?
home?
うち?
what?
なに?
this.
これ
It's soaking wet.
びっしょびしょやん
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's soaking wet.
びっしょびしょになってるね
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Amazing, erotic.
すごい、エロい
Hey.
ねえ
Are you going to put this out?
こんな、出しちゃうの?
Did something like this come out?
こんな、出ちゃったの?
It seems immortal.
不死そうだね
Chinchin, do you like it?
ちんちん、好きなの?
Isn't it a bit slimy?
なんか、ぬるぐるになってない?
Wow, you touch me in an erotic way.
すごい、エロい触り方するね
That kind of touch.
そんな、触り方
Where did you learn it?
どこで覚えたの?
Can you do that without using your hands?
そんな、手を使わずにできるの?
Take it down.
下に下ろして
amazing.
すごい
Wow, it feels good.
すごい、気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいですね
It's delicious.
うまいね
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Awesome, you're good at it.
すごい、上手ね
Soaked.
びっしょ
amazing.
すごい
As expected, the atmosphere is coming out really well.
やっぱ、すっげえ大気出てきてるな
The bed is crap.
ベッドベタだね
Why are you so big?
なんで、そんな、でけえ
Don't you have that kind of study?
そういう勉強もさ、ないの?
Is there more?
してもっとある?
Is it okay?
いいの?
child
こ
What?
っち?
Open your arms and legs properly.
手 足、ちゃんと開いて
Open it firmly.
しっかり開いて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Amazing, it's made of wood.
すごい、しゅうでできてる
Something came out.
なんか、出てきた
amazing.
すごい
Well then,
じゃあ、
yes.
そう
Do this, then.
こう やって、じゃあ、そう
I don't know.
わかんない
Please move so that it feels good.
気持ちいいように、動かしてください
It's so tingling.
すっごい、うずい
I got excited.
テンションについちゃった
fun.
楽しい
Finally, add your feet.
最後に、足を入れしてください
You can see it in places like this.
見えるでしょ、こういったところ
sleep?
眠る?
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
恥ずかしいでしょ
This is amazing.
すごい、これ
That's true.
本当だね
Can I take it out now?
もうさ、出していい?
Can I put it inside?
中に出していい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
What should I do?
どうしよう
good?
いい?
It came out muddy.
泥って出てきた
Do you understand now?
今さ、 わかる?
That's enough.
十分で
It came out like a mess.
めちゃめちゃ出たの
Do you understand?
わかる?
Now it's amazing.
今、すごいすごい
No way.
やだ
This liquid isn't just for me.
これは、俺だけの液体じゃないよね
hey
ね
picture.
え
Let's do it again.
また しようね